Bence Keresztes–Nagy

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

<u>keresztesnagybence@gmail.com</u>

Szentes, Hungary

+36/30-083-70-77

Profile

I am a front-end developer specializing in angular. I began my studies in high school and returned to continue the journey one and a half years ago, beginning with Udemy and online documentation and being advised by a senior mentor in front-end engineering.

Employment History

Angular developer, Offconon, London

September 2022 — January 2023

Working with three other frontend developers on component development, styling, and housekeeping improvements (husky & precommit hooks, linter setup).

Angular developer, Addet web, Vienna

September 2022 — December 2023

Development of components, styling, bug fixes, responsibility enhancements, remote device testing, and direct alignment with owners

Warehouse supervisor, DGP Intelsius Ltd, York

August 2017 — December 2021

Product preparation for on-line sale, including picking and prepping for transportation. Product administration, training, and supervision of a four-person team.

Education

High School Diploma, Information Technology, Pollák Antal Secondary School, Technical School, Szentes

2005 — 2009

Links

Portfolio LinkedIn

Skills

JavaScript	CSS3
HTML5	SCSS
NgRx	RxJs
Git	GitHub
Agile	SCRUM
JIRA	Trello